Finding Aid for the The James D. Squires Papers
Special Collections and University Archives
- Series I: Journalism career (1972-1989)
  - Series II: Ross Perot campaign - RESTRICTED (1992-1995)
    - Box 30: Publications, miscellaneous items, original clippings
      - Publications, Tsongas, Paul. A Call to Economic Arms (Box 30, Folder 15)
      - Publications, Tsongas, Paul. “A Different Road” (Box 30, Folder 16)
      - Publications, Zaller, John and Mark Hunt. “The Rise and Fall of Candidate Perot: Unmediated vs. Mediated Politics.” June 1994 (Box 30, Folder 17)
      - Miscellaneous, explanatory historical note from James Squires (Box 30, Folder 18)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 30, Folder 19)
      - Original correspondence, Bell, Sally-Faria, Paula (Box 30, Folder 20)
      - Original correspondence, Galt, Bill-Hume, Ellen (Box 30, Folder 21)
      - Original correspondence, Jordan, DeSoto-Murphy, Pat (Box 30, Folder 22)
      - Original correspondence, Paulson, Terry-Whittle, Richard (Box 30, Folder 23)
      - Original statement and transcript of NPR interview, May 14, 1992 (Box 30, Folder 24)
      - Original clippings, April 25, 1992-February 27, 1995; n.d. (Box 30, Folder 25)
  - Series III: Books (1992-2003)
    - A Search for Justice
      - Box 31: Manuscripts (Box 31)
      - Manuscript fragments - chapter 1 (Box 31, Folder 1)
      - Manuscript fragments - chapter 2 (Box 31, Folder 2)
      - Manuscript fragments - chapter 6 (Box 31, Folder 3)
      - Manuscript fragments - chapter 13 (Box 31, Folder 4)
      - Manuscript - chapter 1 (Box 31, Folder 5)
      - Manuscript - chapter 2 (Box 31, Folder 6)
      - Manuscript - chapter 3 (Box 31, Folder 7)
      - Manuscript - chapter 4 (Box 31, Folder 8)
      - Manuscript - chapter 5 (Box 31, Folder 9)
      - Manuscript - chapter 6 (Box 31, Folder 10)
      - Manuscript - chapter 7 (Box 31, Folder 11)
      - Manuscript - chapter 8 (Box 31, Folder 12)
      - Manuscript - chapter 9 (Box 31, Folder 13)
      - Manuscript - chapter 10 (Box 31, Folder 14)
      - Manuscript - chapter 11 (Box 31, Folder 15)
      - Manuscript - chapter 12 (Box 31, Folder 16)
      - Manuscript - chapter 13 (Box 31, Folder 17)
      - Manuscript with corrections - chapter 1 (Box 31, Folder 18)
      - Manuscript with corrections - chapter 2 (Box 31, Folder 19)
      - Manuscript with corrections - chapter 3 (Box 31, Folder 20)
      - Manuscript with corrections - chapter 4 (Box 31, Folder 21)
      - Manuscript with corrections - chapter 5 (Box 31, Folder 22)
      - Manuscript with corrections - chapter 6 (Box 31, Folder 23)
      - Manuscript with corrections - chapter 7 (Box 31, Folder 24)
      - Manuscript with corrections - chapter 8 (Box 31, Folder 25)
      - Manuscript with corrections - chapter 9 (Box 31, Folder 26)
      - Manuscript with corrections - chapter 10 (Box 31, Folder 27)
      - Manuscript with corrections - chapter 11 (Box 31, Folder 28)
      - Manuscript with corrections - chapter 12 (Box 31, Folder 29)
      - Manuscript fragment with corrections - chapter 13 (Box 31, Folder 30)
      - Manuscript fragments - chapter 1 (Box 31, Folder 31)
      - Manuscript fragments - chapter 2 (Box 31, Folder 32)
      - Manuscript fragments - chapter 3 (Box 31, Folder 33)
      - Manuscript fragments - chapter 4 (Box 31, Folder 34)
      - Manuscript with corrections - chapter 1 (Box 31, Folder 35)
      - Manuscript with corrections - chapter 2 (Box 31, Folder 36)
      - Manuscript with corrections - chapter 3 (Box 31, Folder 37)
      - Manuscript with corrections - chapter 4 (Box 31, Folder 38)
      - Manuscript with corrections - chapter 5 (Box 31, Folder 39)
      - Manuscript with corrections - chapter 6 (Box 31, Folder 40)
      - Manuscript with corrections - chapter 7 (Box 31, Folder 41)
      - Manuscript with corrections - chapter 8 (Box 31, Folder 42)
      - Manuscript with corrections - chapter 9 (Box 31, Folder 43)
      - Manuscript with corrections - chapter 10 (Box 31, Folder 44)
      - Manuscript with corrections - chapter 11 (Box 31, Folder 45)
      - Manuscript with corrections - chapter 12 (Box 31, Folder 46)
      - Manuscript with corrections - chapter 13 (Box 31, Folder 47)
      - Manuscript fragment (Box 31, Folder 48)
      - Condensed manuscript (Box 31, Folder 49)
      - Manuscript inserts (Box 31, Folder 50)
      - Chapter quotes (Box 31, Folder 51)
    - Box 32: Notes, correspondence, clippings, wire reports, research, photographs, original clippings
      - Notes (Box 32, Folder 1)
      - Incoming correspondence - Margolis, Esther-Toronto Star (Box 32, Folder 2)
      - Outgoing correspondence, February 11, 1968 (Box 32, Folder 3)
      - Clippings, April 18, 1968-November 2, 1968 (Box 32, Folder 4)
      - Clippings, January 19, 1969-March 6, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 5)
      - Wire reports, September 11, 1968-February 8, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 6)
      - Research, Tennessean reports, March 8, 1969-March 13, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 7)
      - Research, wire reports, March 15, 1969-May 24, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 8)
      - Research, Tennessean reports, March 23, 1969-May 24, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 9)
      - Research - wire reports (Box 32, Folder 10)
      - Research - wire reports (Box 32, Folder 11)
      - Research - legal documents (Box 32, Folder 12)
      - Photographs (Box 32, Folder 13)
      - Original clippings, April 20, 1969-n.d. (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Read All About It!
    - Box 33: Manuscripts
      - Manuscript with corrections - introduction (Box 33, Folder 1)
      - Manuscript fragment with corrections - “The Camel and the Frog” chapter (Box 33, Folder 2)
      - Manuscript with corrections - “Peers and Preservationists” chapter (Box 33, Folder 3)
      - Manuscript fragment with corrections - “Penetration and Profits” chapter (Box 33, Folder 4)
      - Manuscript with corrections - “The New Citizen Caine [sic]” chapter (Box 33, Folder 5)
      - Manuscript with corrections - introduction (Box 33, Folder 6)
      - Manuscript with corrections - “The Camel and the Frog” chapter (duplicate page 11) (Box 33, Folder 7)
      - Manuscript with corrections - “Profits and Penetration” chapter (Box 33, Folder 8)
      - Manuscript with corrections - “The New Citizens Caine [sic]” chapter (Box 33, Folder 9)
      - Manuscript fragment - introduction (Box 33, Folder 10)
      - Manuscript with corrections - “Profits and Penetration” chapter (duplicate pages 12-14, 19) (Box 33, Folder 11)
      - Manuscript with corrections - “The New Citizens Caine [sic]” chapter (Box 33, Folder 12)
      - Manuscript with corrections - foreword (Box 33, Folder 13)
      - Manuscript with corrections - chapters 1 and 2 (Box 33, Folder 14)
      - Manuscript with corrections - chapter 3 (Box 33, Folder 15)
      - Manuscript with corrections - chapter 4 (Box 33, Folder 16)
      - Manuscript with corrections - chapter 5 (Box 33, Folder 17)
      - Manuscript with corrections - chapter 6 (Box 33, Folder 18)
      - Manuscript - endnotes (Box 33, Folder 19)
      - Manuscript with corrections - chapter 1 (Box 33, Folder 20)
      - Manuscript with corrections - chapter 2 (Box 33, Folder 21)
      - Manuscript with corrections - chapter 3 (Box 33, Folder 22)
      - Manuscript with corrections - chapter 4 (Box 33, Folder 23)
      - Manuscript with corrections - chapter 5 (Box 33, Folder 24)
      - Manuscript with corrections - chapter 6 (Box 33, Folder 25)
      - Manuscript with corrections - foreword (Box 33, Folder 26)
      - Manuscript with corrections - chapter 1 (Box 33, Folder 27)
      - Manuscript with corrections - chapter 2 (Box 33, Folder 28)
      - Manuscript with corrections - chapter 3 (Box 33, Folder 29)
      - Manuscript with corrections - chapter 4 (Box 33, Folder 30)
      - Manuscript with corrections - chapter 5 (Box 33, Folder 31)
      - Manuscript with corrections - chapter 6 and epilogue (Box 33, Folder 32)
    - Box 34: Manuscripts
      - Incomplete manuscript - foreword (Box 34, Folder 1)
      - Incomplete manuscript - chapter 3 (Box 34, Folder 2)
      - Incomplete manuscript - chapter 4 (Box 34, Folder 3)
      - Incomplete manuscript - chapter 5 (Box 34, Folder 4)
      - Incomplete manuscript - chapter 6 (Box 34, Folder 5)
      - Incomplete manuscript - epilogue (Box 34, Folder 6)
      - Incomplete manuscript - introduction (Box 34, Folder 7)
      - Incomplete manuscript - chapter 3 (Box 34, Folder 8)
      - Incomplete manuscript - chapter 4 (Box 34, Folder 9)
      - Incomplete manuscript - chapter 5 (Box 34, Folder 10)
      - Incomplete manuscript - chapter 6 (Box 34, Folder 11)
      - Incomplete manuscript - epilogue (Box 34, Folder 12)
      - Manuscript - foreword (Box 34, Folder 13)
      - Manuscript - chapter 1 (Box 34, Folder 14)
      - Manuscript - chapter 2 (Box 34, Folder 15)
      - Manuscript - chapter 3 (Box 34, Folder 16)
      - Manuscript - chapter 4 (Box 34, Folder 17)
      - Manuscript - chapter 5 (Box 34, Folder 18)
      - Manuscript - chapter 6 (Box 34, Folder 19)
      - Manuscript - epilogue (Box 34, Folder 20)
      - Manuscript - foreword (Box 34, Folder 21)
      - Incomplete manuscript - chapter 1 (Box 34, Folder 22)
      - Manuscript - chapter 2 (Box 34, Folder 23)
      - Incomplete manuscript - chapter 3 (Box 34, Folder 24)
      - Manuscript - foreword (Box 34, Folder 25)
      - Manuscript - chapter 1 (Box 34, Folder 26)
      - Manuscript - chapter 2 (Box 34, Folder 27)
      - Manuscript - chapter 3 (Box 34, Folder 28)
      - Manuscript - chapter 4 (Box 34, Folder 29)
      - Manuscript - chapter 6 and epilogue (chapter 5 missing) (Box 34, Folder 30)
      - Manuscript - endnotes (Box 34, Folder 31)
      - Manuscript - introduction (Box 34, Folder 32)
      - Manuscript - chapter 1 (Box 34, Folder 33)
      - Manuscript - chapter 2 (Box 34, Folder 34)
      - Manuscript - chapter 3 (Box 34, Folder 35)
      - Manuscript - chapter 4 (Box 34, Folder 36)
      - Manuscript - chapter 5 (Box 34, Folder 37)
      - Manuscript - chapter 6 (Box 34, Folder 38)
      - Manuscript - chapter 7 (Box 34, Folder 39)
      - Manuscript - chapter 8 (Box 34, Folder 40)
    - Box 35: Manuscripts
      - Manuscript with corrections - foreword (Box 35, Folder 1)
      - Manuscript with corrections - chapter 1 (Box 35, Folder 2)
      - Manuscript with corrections - chapter 2 (Box 35, Folder 3)
      - Manuscript with corrections - chapter 3 (Box 35, Folder 4)
      - Manuscript with corrections - chapter 4 (Box 35, Folder 5)
      - Manuscript with corrections - chapter 5 (Box 35, Folder 6)
      - Manuscript with corrections - chapter 6 (Box 35, Folder 7)
      - Manuscript - foreword (Box 35, Folder 8)
      - Manuscript - chapter 1 (Box 35, Folder 9)
      - Manuscript - chapter 2 (Box 35, Folder 10)
      - Manuscript - chapter 3 (Box 35, Folder 11)
      - Manuscript - chapter 4 (Box 35, Folder 12)
      - Manuscript - chapter 5 (Box 35, Folder 13)
      - Manuscript - chapter 6 (Box 35, Folder 14)
      - Manuscript - chapter 7 (Box 35, Folder 15)
      - Manuscript - chapter 8 (Box 35, Folder 16)
      - Manuscript fragment with corrections (Box 35, Folder 17)
      - Manuscript fragment - chapter 1 (Box 35, Folder 18)
      - Manuscript fragment - chapter 3 (Box 35, Folder 19)
      - Manuscript fragments (Box 35, Folder 20)
      - Manuscript fragments (Box 35, Folder 21)
      - Manuscript fragments (Box 35, Folder 22)
      - Manuscript fragments (duplicate last page) (Box 35, Folder 23)
      - Manuscript fragments (Box 35, Folder 24)
      - Manuscript fragments (Box 35, Folder 25)
      - Manuscript fragments (Box 35, Folder 26)
      - Manuscript fragments (Box 35, Folder 27)
      - Manuscript fragments (Box 35, Folder 28)
      - Manuscript fragments (Box 35, Folder 29)
    - Box 36: Manuscript, galleys, manuscript fragments, notes, speeches, correspondence
      - Galleys - chapters 1-2 (Box 36, Folder 1)
      - Galleys - chapters 3-4 (Box 36, Folder 2)
      - Galleys - chapters 5-6 (Box 36, Folder 3)
      - Galleys - chapters 7-8 (missing galley no. 96) (Box 36, Folder 4)
      - Galleys - chapter 9 (Box 36, Folder 5)
      - Dedication (Box 36, Folder 6)
      - Flap copy, back copy, cover mockup (Box 36, Folder 7)
      - Notes (Box 36, Folder 8)
      - Notes (Box 36, Folder 9)
      - Speech (Box 36, Folder 10)
      - Incoming correspondence - Bradlee, Benjamin-Eisendrath, Charles (Box 36, Folder 11)
      - Incoming correspondence - Fabens, Andrew (Box 36, Folder 12)
      - Incoming correspondence - Fure, Jonathan-Kwan, Debbie (Box 36, Folder 13)
      - Incoming correspondence - Lawrence, Starling-Negin, Elliott (Box 36, Folder 14)
      - Incoming correspondence - Quine, Frank-Risser, James (Box 36, Folder 15)
      - Incoming correspondence - Stern, William (Box 36, Folder 16)
      - Incoming correspondence - Stiles-Gaudry, Jennifer-Wickham, Suzanne; unidentified (Box 36, Folder 17)
      - Outgoing correspondence, January 10, 1990-May 14, 1990 (Box 36, Folder 18)
      - Outgoing correspondence, April 16, 1991-October 7, 1991 (Box 36, Folder 19)
      - Outgoing correspondence - n.d. (Box 36, Folder 20)
    - Box 37: Correspondence, clippings, publications, miscellaneous
      - Clippings, October 3, 1988- September 26, 1991 (Box 37, Folder 1)
      - Clippings, January 13, 1992-January 31, 1993 (Box 37, Folder 2)
      - Clippings, February 8, 1993-July 31, 1993; n.d. (Box 37, Folder 3)
      - Publications, Business Week February 22, 1993 (Box 37, Folder 4)
      - Publications, Kiwanis Club of South Orlando newsletter (Box 37, Folder 5)
      - Publications, New Perspective Quarterly Fall 1992 (Box 37, Folder 6)
      - Publications, Northshore July 1993 (Box 37, Folder 7)
      - Publications, Orlando January 1993 (Box 37, Folder 8)
      - Speech, Burl Osborne at the American Society of Newspaper Editors annual meeting in Boston, MA on April 12, 1991 (Box 37, Folder 9)
      - Essay, October 4, 1985 (Box 37, Folder 10)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 37, Folder 11)
      - Original correspondence - Fabens, Andrew-Kwan, Debbie (Box 37, Folder 12)
      - Original correspondence - McKinney, Robert - Wickham, Suzanne (Box 37, Folder 13)
      - Original clippings, March 15, 1991-January 29, 1993 (Box 37, Folder 14)
      - Original clippings, January 31, 1993-November 3, 1997; n.d. (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - Secrets of the Hopewell Box
    - Box 38: Drafts, proofs, correspondence, speeches, notes, photographs and negatives
      - Draft index (Box 38, Folder 1)
      - Draft flap copy, dedication, bibliography, acknowledgements (Box 38, Folder 2)
      - Dummy proofs - cover and text (Box 38, Folder 3)
      - Incoming correspondence - Beasley, John S. II-Vick, Robert D. Sr. (Box 38, Folder 4)
      - Incoming correspondence - Weisser, Will-Woods, Frank A.; unidentified (Box 38, Folder 5)
      - Outgoing correspondence - n.d. (Fecych, Ruth-Woods, Frank A.) (Box 38, Folder 6)
      - Speeches (Box 38, Folder 7)
      - Speech drafts and notes (Box 38, Folder 8)
      - Notes (Box 38, Folder 9)
      - Notes (Box 38, Folder 10)
      - Notes (Box 38, Folder 11)
      - Notes (Box 38, Folder 12)
      - Photographs (8x10) (Box 38, Folder 13)
      - Photographs (8x10) (Box 38, Folder 14)
      - Photographs (5x7) (Box 38, Folder 15)
      - Photograph negatives (Box 38, Folder 16)
      - Photograph negatives (Box 38, Folder 17)
    - Box 39: Research - Individuals
      - Alessio, Al (Box 39, Folder 1)
      - Barnes, James F. “Slo” (Box 39, Folder 2)
      - Bomar, Lynn (Box 39, Folder 3)
      - Briley, Beverly (see also Hickman, Litton) (Box 39, Folder 4)
      - Craig, Edwin (Box 39, Folder 5)
      - Doyle, Frances (Box 39, Folder 6)
      - Flippen, H.E. (Box 39, Folder 7)
      - Garfinkle, Elkin (Box 39, Folder 8)
      - Gorrell, Frank (Box 39, Folder 9)
      - Graves, C.D. “Cootchie” (Box 39, Folder 10)
      - Harwell, Kenneth (Box 39, Folder 11)
      - Hickman, Litton and Beverly Briley (Box 39, Folder 12)
      - Jackson, J.J. (Box 39, Folder 13)
      - Jacobs, Gene “Little Evil” (Box 39, Folder 14)
      - Jett, Leslie (Box 39, Folder 15)
      - Lawson, James M. (Box 39, Folder 16)
      - Lewis, John (Box 39, Folder 17)
      - Lewis, John (Box 39, Folder 18)
      - Looby, Z. Alexander (Box 39, Folder 19)
      - Loser, J. Carlton (Box 39, Folder 20)
      - O’Brien, Charles (Box 39, Folder 21)
      - Onohundro, John (Box 39, Folder 22)
      - Osborn, Vick Sr. (Box 39, Folder 23)
      - Pickle, V.H. (Box 39, Folder 24)
      - Pierce, Webb and Ray Stevens (Box 39, Folder 25)
      - Reasoner, Dude (Box 39, Folder 26)
      - Riley, Charlie (Box 39, Folder 27)
      - Roberson, Jim (Box 39, Folder 28)
      - Robinson, Garner (Box 39, Folder 29)
      - Sheridan, Jake (Box 39, Folder 30)
      - Smith, Kelly Miller (Box 39, Folder 31)
      - Stahlman, Gladys (Box 39, Folder 32)
      - Stahlman, James G. (Box 39, Folder 33)
      - Stokes, Walter (Box 39, Folder 34)
      - Washer, James (Box 39, Folder 35)
      - Weaver, William (Box 39, Folder 36)
      - White, Weldon (Box 39, Folder 37)
    - Box 40: Research - Events
      - 1945 (November) and 1946 (August) election returns (Box 40, Folder 1)
      - 1946 Election suit (Box 40, Folder 2)
      - 1947 Cummings-White election (Box 40, Folder 3)
      - 1950 Browning-Allen election; 1950 sheriff’s race (Box 40, Folder 4)
      - 1950 Sheriff’s race - Garfinkle, Sheridan, Robinson (Box 40, Folder 5)
      - 1951 West-Cummings election and returns (Box 40, Folder 6)
      - 1952 Capps election - Lewis Hurt (Box 40, Folder 7)
      - 1952 Clement campaign and sheriff’s race (Box 40, Folder 8)
      - 1952 Clement returns (August and November) (Box 40, Folder 9)
      - 1952 Quarterly Court (Box 40, Folder 10)
      - 1954-1955 Quarterly Court (Box 40, Folder 11)
      - 1956 Loser-West election (Box 40, Folder 12)
      - 1962 Election and returns (Box 40, Folder 13)
      - 1963 Nashville Police Department overhaul (Box 40, Folder 14)
      - 1963 Nashville Police Department overhaul - initial African-American officers (Box 40, Folder 15)
      - 1966 Elections and returns (Box 40, Folder 16)
      - Belle Meade Club (Box 40, Folder 17)
      - Browning-Kefauver victory (Box 40, Folder 18)
      - Carroll shooting (Box 40, Folder 19)
      - Colmere Club (Box 40, Folder 20)
      - Columbia Riots (Box 40, Folder 21)
      - Gambling - General (Box 40, Folder 22)
      - Gambling - Washer-Barnes (Box 40, Folder 23)
      - Lunch counter sit-ins (Box 40, Folder 24)
      - Old Hickory Village report, August 1929 (Box 40, Folder 25)
      - Tennessean history (Box 40, Folder 26)
    - Box 41: Research - Trials, miscellaneous, clippings, publications, original faxes and clippings
      - Jimmy Hoffa trial, 1962 (Box 41, Folder 1)
      - Jimmy Hoffa trial, 1962 (Box 41, Folder 2)
      - Jimmy Hoffa trial, 1962 (Box 41, Folder 3)
      - USA vs. Z.T. Osborn Jr. (Box 41, Folder 4)
      - USA vs. Z.T. Osborn Jr. (Box 41, Folder 5)
      - USA vs. Z.T. Osborn Jr. (Box 41, Folder 6)
      - USA vs. Z.T. Osborn Jr. (Box 41, Folder 7)
      - USA vs. Z.T. Osborn Jr. - Petition for rehearing (Box 41, Folder 8)
      - USA vs. Z.T. Osborn Jr. - Appellant’s appendix on appeal (Box 41, Folder 9)
      - USA vs. Z.T. Osborn Jr. - D.L. Landsden’s testimony (Box 41, Folder 10)
      - West vs. Sheridan-Garfinkle Machine (Box 41, Folder 11)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 41, Folder 12)
      - Clippings, November/December 1994-July 28, 1996 (Box 41, Folder 13)
      - Publications - Home Place: A History of the Hillsboro-West End Neighborhood (Box 41, Folder 14)
      - Publications - Old Hickory … the First 75 Years (Box 41, Folder 15)
      - Publications - Our Old Hickory Heritage (Box 41, Folder 16)
      - Original faxes and clippings (Box 41, Folder 17)
      - Original faxes and clippings (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - Horse of a Different Color
    - Box 42: Manuscripts
      - 1st Manuscript with corrections - preface and chapter 1 (Box 42, Folder 1)
      - 1st Manuscript with corrections - chapters 2-3 (Box 42, Folder 2)
      - 1st Manuscript with corrections - chapters 4-5 (Box 42, Folder 3)
      - 1st Manuscript with corrections - chapters 6-7 (Box 42, Folder 4)
      - 1st Manuscript with corrections - chapters 8-9 (Box 42, Folder 5)
      - 1st Manuscript with corrections - chapters 10-11 (Box 42, Folder 6)
      - 1st Manuscript with corrections - chapter 12 (Box 42, Folder 7)
      - 1st Manuscript with corrections - chapters 13-14 (Box 42, Folder 8)
      - 1st Manuscript with corrections - chapters 15-16 (Box 42, Folder 9)
      - 1st Manuscript with corrections - chapters 17-18 (Box 42, Folder 10)
      - 1st Manuscript with corrections - chapters 19-20 (Box 42, Folder 11)
      - 1st Manuscript with corrections - chapters 21-22 (Box 42, Folder 12)
      - 1st Manuscript with corrections - afterword (Box 42, Folder 13)
      - 2nd Manuscript with corrections - prologue and chapter 1 (Box 42, Folder 14)
      - 2nd Manuscript with corrections - chapters 2-3 (Box 42, Folder 15)
      - 2nd Manuscript with corrections - chapters 4-5 (Box 42, Folder 16)
      - 2nd Manuscript with corrections - chapters 6-7 (Box 42, Folder 17)
      - 2nd Manuscript with corrections - chapters 8-9 (Box 42, Folder 18)
      - 2nd Manuscript with corrections - chapters 10-11 (Box 42, Folder 19)
      - 2nd Manuscript with corrections - chapter 12 (Box 42, Folder 20)
      - 2nd Manuscript with corrections - chapters 13-14 (Box 42, Folder 21)
      - 2nd Manuscript with corrections - chapters 15-16 (Box 42, Folder 22)
      - 2nd Manuscript with corrections - chapters 17-18 (Box 42, Folder 23)
      - 2nd Manuscript with corrections - chapter 19 (Box 42, Folder 24)
    - Box 43: Manuscripts
      - Final manuscript for recording - prologue and chapter 1 (Box 43, Folder 1)
      - Final manuscript for recording - chapters 2-3 (Box 43, Folder 2)
      - Final manuscript for recording - chapters 4-5 (Box 43, Folder 3)
      - Final manuscript for recording - chapters 6-7 (Box 43, Folder 4)
      - Final manuscript for recording - chapters 8-9 (Box 43, Folder 5)
      - Final manuscript for recording - chapters 10-11 (Box 43, Folder 6)
      - Final manuscript for recording - chapter 12 (Box 43, Folder 7)
      - Final manuscript for recording - chapters 13-14 (Box 43, Folder 8)
      - Final manuscript for recording - chapters 15-16 (Box 43, Folder 9)
      - Final manuscript for recording - chapters 17-18 (Box 43, Folder 10)
      - Final manuscript for recording - chapter 19 and afterword (Box 43, Folder 11)
      - Final manuscript for recording - afterword fragment (Box 43, Folder 12)
      - Manuscript - preface and chapter 1 (Box 43, Folder 13)
      - Manuscript - chapters 2-3 (Box 43, Folder 14)
      - Manuscript - chapters 4-5 (Box 43, Folder 15)
      - Manuscript - chapters 6-7 (Box 43, Folder 16)
      - Manuscript - chapters 8-9 (Box 43, Folder 17)
      - Manuscript - chapters 10-11 (Box 43, Folder 18)
      - Manuscript - chapter 12 (Box 43, Folder 19)
      - Manuscript - chapter 13-14 (Box 43, Folder 20)
      - Manuscript - chapter 15-16 (Box 43, Folder 21)
      - Manuscript - chapter 17-18 (Box 43, Folder 22)
      - Manuscript - chapter 19 and afterword (Box 43, Folder 23)
      - Manuscript fragment - introduction (Box 43, Folder 24)
      - Manuscript fragment - chapter 2 (Box 43, Folder 25)
      - Manuscript fragments (Box 43, Folder 26)
      - Manuscript fragments (Box 43, Folder 27)
      - Manuscript fragments (Box 43, Folder 28)
      - Cover print and dummy proofs (Box 43, Folder 29)
    - Box 44: Notes, correspondence, miscellaneous, clippings
      - Notes (Box 44, Folder 1)
      - Notes (Box 44, Folder 2)
      - Phone messages (Box 44, Folder 3)